



About me

Highly creative and multitalented Designer with extensive experience in multimedia, marketing, and print design along with Ui & Ux. Exceptional collaborative and interpersonal skills with well-developed written and verbal communication abilities. Passionate and inventive creator of innovative marketing strategies and campaigns.

Contact info

Address:

#208/45, Subramani Garden, 2nd St, Perambur, Chennai - 600 011.

E-mail/Web:

guna_k20@yahoo.com

Phone:

- +91 76678 93888
- +91 89390 27027

Scan the QR code and visit my portfolio

Guna Sekaran K

2D & Web Graphics | Digital Marketing Analyst

Experience

CREATIVE LEAD

Slate and Pencil Pvt Ltd

Jan 2020 - Jun 2022

The purpose of this job is to create a visual representation of a company's brand, product, or services & running digital campaigns. I'm in charge of the design and branding of an organization's materials & digital medium. We work as a team to create print designs and other promotional materials, as well as digital graphics like websites, apps, and animations.

Sr. GRAPHIC AND UI/UX

Feb 2017 - Jan 2020

Image infotainment

Teaching software classes, and design fundamentals to students and to create brand guidelines corporate teams. Working with the inhouse design team on print and digital collateral and also with onsite & technical SEO.

2D GRAPHIC AND ANIMATOR

Apr 2011 - Feb 2017

Dream Zone

Making 2D and 3D animations for advertising purposes & Brand Identity. Creating layouts for websites and e-publications. Teaching design software to college students.

Education

BACHELOR DEGREE / Electronics

2003 - 2006

Sri Ram College

The study of Analog Electronics, Electromagnetic, Digital System Design, Communications

Personal skill

Branding	Photoshop
Print design	Illustrator
Restoration	Indesign
Color Grading	Lightroom
Layout & Compositing	After Effects
Packaging	Premiere Pro / Audition
2D Animation	Final Cut Pro

* PWD : Yes - Locomotor disability 80%

* Currently working as a Freelancer

